(Penny:)will you promise
to stop pestering me
(Penny:)about Leonard and Priya?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
Sure.
(Penny:)All right. I'll go change.
Come on in.
(Amy:)If you'd have let me
bring the chloroform,
(Amy:)we wouldn't have had to put up
with all this jibber-jabber.
(Zack:)Anyway, after we
get done snowboarding,
(Zack:)I go back to the lodge
and get in the Jacuzzi.
(Zack:)There's no one around, so
naturally, I'm free-balling it.
(Zack:)Next thing I know,
(Zack:)this beautiful chick shows up,
(Zack:)drunk out of her skull,
wants to get in with me.
(Sheldon:)Question.
(Sheldon:)Was it a Jacuzzi or a hot tub?
Really? That's
your question?
(Zack:)What's the difference?
"Jacuzzi" is a commercial brand.
"Hot tub" is the generic term.
(Sheldon:)I.E., all Jacuzzis
(Sheldon:)are hot tubs,
(Sheldon:)but not all
hot tubs are Jacuzzis.
(Zack:)Is that like
all thumbs are fingers,
(Zack:)but not all fingers are thumbs?
(Sheldon:)Surprisingly, yes.
(Sheldon:)Nice.
(Zack:)Now, what exactly are toes?